{
    "subject": "Alan_Rudolph",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Afterglow__film_",
    "human_readable": "Alan Rudolph created the film Afterglow.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.910830020904541,
            "question": "What type of work did Alan Rudolph create titled Afterglow?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8445031046867371,
            "question": "What is the title of the film created by Alan Rudolph?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7700159549713135,
            "question": "What did Alan Rudolph create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7572808265686035,
            "question": "Is Afterglow a film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7563609480857849,
            "question": "Who directed the film Afterglow?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7420678734779358,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Alan Rudolph."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6043335199356079,
            "question": "Who is the director behind the movie Afterglow?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49094653129577637,
            "question": "Name an example of a film by Alan Rudolph."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45721566677093506,
            "question": "What is the name of the director who made Afterglow?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41581717133522034,
            "question": "Can you tell me about a film directed by Alan Rudolph?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Alan Rudolph created the film Afterglow.",
            "html": "yago_9746_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the director who made Afterglow?",
            "html": "yago_9746_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name an example of a film by Alan Rudolph.",
            "html": "yago_9746_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is the director behind the movie Afterglow?",
            "html": "yago_9746_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9746_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9746_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9746_140.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9746_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9746_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9746_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9746_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9746_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9746_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9746_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that \"Afterglow\" has the following characteristics:\n\n* It's a film directed by Alan Rudolph.\n* The original film title and English title are both \"Afterglow\".\n* The year it was released is 1997.\n\nAdditionally, one of the documents mentions that the director, Alan Rudolph, had a new film: Afterglow. This implies that he created or made the film.\n\nTherefore, the information in the documents supports the triple that Alan Rudolph created the film Afterglow."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents indicate that Alan Rudolph is indeed the writer-director of the film \"Afterglow,\" which was released in 1997. Therefore, the statement \"Alan Rudolph created the film Afterglow\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}